我好想念茱莉
Man,I sure miss Julie.
西班牙侏儒
Spanish midgets.
跟西班牙侏儒摔跤的是…
Spanish midgets wrestling....
茱莉！哦，我明白你是怎么想到她的了
Julie! Okay,I see how you got there.
你有想过电话用来做什么吗？
You ever figure out what that thing's for?
我在过滤电话
I'm trying this screening thing.
我想如果我老是去接的话 大家会以为我没有生活
If I always answer the phone,people will think I have no life.
老天啊，罗德里格从未被压住
My God! Rodrigo never gets pinned!
听到哔声后 知道该怎么做吧？
At the sound of the beep,you know what to do.
我要找鲍勃
Hello. I'm looking for Bob.
我是珍德
This is Jade.
我不知道你的电话改了没有 不过我不断在想…
I don 't know if you 're still at this number,but I was thinking...
…我们过去那段美好的时光 我知道都已经三年了啦…
...about how great it was. I know it's been three years...
…可是我希望我们能够重修旧好
...but I was hoping we could hook up again.
我提不起勇气打电话…
I barely had the nerve to make this call...
…你知道我怎么样吗？ 怎么样？
-...so you know what I did? -What?
我喝得醉醺醺…
I got a little drunk...
…还一丝不挂
...and naked.
我是鲍勃
Bob here!
六人行 第2季 第05集 五块牛排和一根茄子
The One With Five Steaks and An Eggplant
你近来都在干什么呢？
So what have you been up to?
跟平常一样啊
Oh,you know,the usual.
教有氧舞蹈…
Teaching aerobics...
…玩得太疯狂
...partying way too much.
如果你想知道的话…
And in case you wondered...
…新007电影海报上那双腿 是我的
... those are my legs on the new James Bond poster.
请等一下，我有电话进来了
Can you hold on? I have another call.
我爱她 我知道
-I love her! -I know.
我回来了 那我们到底要不要聚一聚啊？
-I'm back. -So are we gonna get together?
当然要了
Absolutely.
明天下午怎么样？
How about tomorrow afternoon?
你知道中央公园咖啡厅吗？五点钟左右
Do you know Central Perk? Say,five-ish?
太棒了，到时候见
Great. I'll see you then.
我装上电话，终于物有所值了
Having a phone has finally paid off.
就算你装鲍勃装得很像…
You do a good Bob impression...
…等到她明天一看到你…
... but when she sees you tomorrow...
…就会发现你不是鲍勃了
...she's gonna realize you're not Bob.
你看纹身
You see Tattoo....
珍德希望跟鲍勃重修旧好
Jade's fantasy is to rekindle the love she had with Bob.
而我希望你能像个正常人一样说话
My fantasy is that you talk like a normal person.
我只希望当她知道 鲍勃放她鸽子的时候…
I'm hoping that when Bob doesn't show up...
…她会投向邻桌的 陌生人的怀抱
...she'll seek comfort in the arms of the stranger at the next table.
老天，你真是邪恶到家
Oh,my God. You are pure evil.
邪恶到家…
Okay,pure evil...
…饥渴兼孤单
... horny and alone.
这我都试过了
I've done this.
对，大家都在
Yeah,everybody's here.
各位，跟在新墨西哥州的茱莉 打声招呼吧
Hey,everybody! Say hi to Julie in New Mexico!
茱莉…
Hi,Julie.
趁罗斯在讲电话…
While Ross is on the phone...
…每人缴62块庆祝他的生日
...everybody owes me 62 bucks for his birthday.
你可不可以将就一下…
Is there any chance that you're rounding up from...
…譬如说…
...you know...
…每个人缴20块就好了
...from like 20?
拜托 要有礼物，演唱会，还有蛋糕
Hey,we got the gift,the concert and the cake.
我们还需要一个蛋糕？
Do we need a cake?
各位，我知道这数目有一点高（有“大起大落”的意思）
I know it's a little steep.
不过是罗斯的生日呀
But it's Ross.
是罗斯
It's Ross.
好了，咱们待会儿见 我还得去…
See you later. I gotta go...
…做一件事
...do a thing!
好了，甜心，我晚上再打给你
Okay,sweetheart,I'll call you later.
你不是真的要那么做吧，老兄
You're not going through with this,are you?
我非做不可
You know,I think I might just.
你们晚上吃什么？
What are you guys doing for dinner tonight?
我想我要开始 为罗斯的生日存钱了
Well,I gotta start saving up for Ross' birthday.
我想我将在家里吃肮脏邦尼兔
I guess I'll just stay home and eat dust bunnies.
你知道这个可要花很多钱啊
Can you believe how much this costs?
你们有时候会不会觉得…
Do you guys ever get the feeling that...
…钱德，他们…
... Chandler and those guys...
…根本不明白 我们赚的钱没他们多
...don't get that we don't make that much money?
他们总是说 “咱们去这儿，去那儿”
They always say let's go here,let's go there.
好像我们能负担得起去这里去哪里似的
Like we can afford to go here and there.
而且我们总是得去“好地方” 你知道吗？
Yes,and we always have to go to,you know,someplace nice.
我们连反对的权利都没有 因为这是庆祝生日…
And we can't say anything about it,because this is a birthday thing...
…罗斯的
...and it's "for Ross."
罗斯的…
For Ross.
老天
Oh,my God!
我在上班…
I'm at work...
…跟平常的一天一样 切切切，煎煎煎
...just an ordinary day,chop,chop,saute,saute.
突然间呢，我们经理里昂 叫我去他的办公室
Suddenly,Leon,the manager,calls me into his office.
原来他们开除了午餐大厨 你们猜谁取代他的职位了？
They fired the lunch chef,and guess who got the job?
如果不是你的话 这可是个糟透的故事
If it's not you,this is a horrible story.
幸好，那个人是我
Fortunately,it is me.
他们还升我为采购主任 谢谢
And they made me head of purchasing,thank you!
太棒了
That's so cool!
我认为我们该出去庆祝一下
Anyway,I think we should go out and celebrate.
去个好地方
You know,someplace nice.
Someplace nice.
你们想我的肾能够卖多少钱？
How much you think I can get for my kidney?
说真的，你不能够这么做
You can't do this.
少来了，拘泥于那种传统方法 我永远把不到那种女孩
I can't get a girl like that with conventional methods.
那有什么关系呢？
It doesn't matter.
她要找的是鲍勃 鲍勃一定是她理想的对象
She wanted to call Bob. Bob could be who she was meant to be with.
你这么做 或许会毁了两个人快乐的机会
You may be destroying their chance for happiness.
我们不认识鲍勃
We don't know Bob.
我们认识我，我们喜欢我 拜托，让我快乐起来
We know me. We like me. Please let me be happy.
你过去告诉那个女人实话
Go over there and tell that woman the truth.
好吧
All right.
去啊
Go.
我要…
Listen,I have to....
我要跟你坦白一件事
I have to confess something.
什么事？
Yes?
放你鸽子的人是混蛋
Whoever stood you up is a jerk.
你怎么会… 我不知道
-How did you -I don't know.
我就是有这种怪怪的感应 我就这样，怪怪的又敏感
I just had this weird sense. But that's me,I'm weird and sensitive.
面纸？
Tissue?
谢谢
Thanks.
不用，你整包留着吧
No,you keep the pack.
我已经哭了一天了
I'm all cried out today.
我敬我刚刚被升为午餐大厨的妹妹一杯
Here is to my sister,the newly appointed head lunch chef.
而且她还接掌了采买大权
Also in charge of purchasing.
恭贺她升为午餐大厨 并且接掌采买大权…
Head lunch chef,also in charge of purchasing
罗兰德不在的时候还有自己的小办公桌
Who has her own little desk when Roland's not there.
午餐大厨，采购，罗兰德不在时 有自己的小办公桌
Lunch chef,purchasing,own little desk when Roland's not there...
咱们敬我的… 等等…我还有传呼机
-... here's to my -Wait! And I got a beeper!
没关系，我等好了
That's fine,I'll just wait.
抱歉…
Sorry.
敬莫妮卡
Monica!
各位可以点菜了吗？
Are we ready to order?
对不起，我们还没看菜单
We haven't even looked yet.
那你们看过之后再叫我
When you do,let me know.
我会在那边引颈企盼的
I'll be over there on the edge of my seat.
你们看看这上面的价钱
Look at these prices!
是呀，都是钱啊
Yeah,these are pretty "cha-ching."
这是些什么？名牌鸡吗？
I know! What are these,famous chickens?
抱歉，我迟到了 莫妮卡，恭喜你
Sorry I'm late. Congratulations,Mon.
我不后悔我迟到，我跟珍德的午后约会太不可思议了
I'm not sorry I'm late. How incredible was my afternoon with Jade?
根据她在我答录机上 留给你的话的确很不可思议
Pretty incredible,according to the message on my machine.
钱德，这个女人为什么 会在我的答录机留话给你呢？
Why is this woman leaving a message for you on my machine?
我必须要告诉她 我的号码是你的号码…
I told her that my number was yours...
…因为我不能告诉她 我的号码是我的号码…
... because I couldn't tell her it was mine...
…因为她以为 我的号码是鲍勃的号码
... because she thinks my number is Bob's number.
你再告诉我一次 结绳先生打来的时候我怎么办？
Tell me again. What do I do when Mr. Roper calls?
可以点菜了吗？
Do I dare ask?
好，我要先来一份生牛肉 然后再来一份烤虾
I'll start with the carpaccio,and then the grilled prawns.
听起来不错，我也一样
Great,same for me.
那这位先生呢？
And for the gentleman?
我要泰国鸡肉披萨
I'll have the Thai chicken pizza.
如果我的披萨少加干果，大蒜…
But if I get it without the nuts and leeks and stuff...
…会不会比较便宜啊？
...is it cheaper?
你是那么想吗？
You'd think,wouldn't you?
好了，我想要点…伴碟沙拉
I will have the side salad.
那要伴在什么菜旁边呢？
And what would that be on the side of?
我不知道
I don't know.
你就帮我放在我的水旁边好了
Just put it right here next to my water.
那你呢？
And for you?
我想我要来一碗黄瓜汤…
I'm gonna have a cup of the cucumber soup and...
…保重了
...take care.
我要一份黑椒鲶鱼
I will have the Cajun catfish.
就这样吗？
Anything else?
还有一首“温柔地杀死我” 怎么样？
Yes,how about a verse of "Killing Me Softly"?
你会朝我的鱼打喷嚏 对不对？
You're gonna sneeze in my fish,aren't you?
-有没有人觉得他们刚生了个外星人 -是的
Does anybody else feel like they just gave birth to an alien? Yes
不
No
加上小费再除以六…
Plus tip,divided by six....
好了，每个人给我28块钱
Everyone owes 28 bucks.
每个人？
Everyone?
你说得对，对不起
Oh! You're right,I'm sorry.
谢谢
Thank you.
今天是莫妮卡的大日子 她不需要付啊
It's Monica's big night. She shouldn't pay.
用五个人去除…
So five of us is...
…每个人33.5元
...33. 50 a piece.
不行，抱歉 那是不可能的事
No. No way. Sorry,not gonna happen.
毕业舞会重演
Prom night flashback.
对不起，莫妮卡 你升了职我替你高兴…
Sorry,Monica. I'm happy you got promoted...
…可是冷黄瓜糊要三十几块？
... but cold cucumber mush for 30-something bucks?
不行
No!
瑞秋只点了那盘小沙拉…
Rachel just had that little salad...
…乔伊只吃了那片小披萨
...and Joey with his teeny pizza!
好吧，菲比
Okay,Pheebs.
那我们就各付各的，好吗？
How about we'll each pay for what we had?
小事一桩嘛
It's no big deal.
对你来讲就是
Not for you.
到底怎么了？
All right,what's going on?
算了，各位 我现在真的不想谈这个
I don't wanna get into this right now.
我觉得 这样只会让大家心里有疙瘩
It'll make everybody uncomfortable.
拜托，说出来吧
You can tell us.
对啊，是我们，没关系的
Yeah,hello? It's us. We'll be fine.
我们三个…
We three...
…觉得…
...feel like that...
…你们有时候不太明白…
...sometimes you guys don't get that....
我们没你们那么有钱
We don't have as much money as you.
我懂了
I hear you.
那我们可以谈啊
We can talk about that.
那么…
Well,then...
…我们就
...Iet's.
我猜我只是 从没想过钱是个问题
I guess I just never think of money as an issue.
那是因为你有钱 你说得好
-Because you have it. -Good point!
你们以前为何不提出来讨论呢？
So how come you guys haven't talked about this before?
因为总是有特别的事情 像莫妮卡的新工作…
Because it's always something. Like with Monica's new job...
…或是罗斯的生日套圈游戏什么的…
...or the whole Ross' birthday hoopla.
我可不希望我的生日 造成任何的不愉快…
I don't want my birthday to be the source of any kind of negative....
你们要为我搞套圈游戏吗？
There's gonna be a hoopla?
基本上有这件事啦 然后又是那件事…
Basically there's the thing,and then the stuff after the thing
如果大家觉得好过一点的话 我们可以忘了那件事…
If it makes anybody feel better,forget the thing...
…只送礼物就好了
...and we'll just do the gift.
礼物？除了礼物还有别的？
Gift? The thing's not the gift?
不，那件事就是我们要去看 “猫头鹰和河豚鱼”（著名演唱组合）
No,we were gonna go see Hootie and the Blowfish.
猫头鹰和…
Hootie and the
我可以听收音机就好了
I can catch them on the radio.
不，现在我愧疚了 你想去听那场演唱会的？
No. Now I feel bad. You wanna go to the concert.
不，听着，那是我的生日…
No,look. It's my birthday...
…最重要的 是我们大家一起过
...and the important thing is that we're all together.
全部 一起过
-All of us. -Together.
不是去演唱会
Not at the concert.
谢谢
Thank you.
那个伊波拉病毒… 得了一定很惨
So,the Ebola virus. That's gotta suck,huh?
莫妮卡，袋子里有什么？
Gee,Monica. What's in the bag?
不知道，钱德 咱们看一下吧
I don't know,Chandler. Let's take a look.
像在演短剧
Oh,it's like a skit.
是六个人的晚餐 五块牛排…
Why,it's dinner for six. Five steaks...
…跟菲比的茄子
...and an eggplant for Phoebe.
我们餐厅换了肉食供应商 新供应商送了我这些牛排谢我
We switched suppliers at work,and they gave me the steaks as a thank-you.
等等，还有啊… 钱德，那信封里头还有什么？
But wait,there's more. Chandler,what is in that envelope?
对了，刚才在外面排演 没这么蠢的
By the way,this didn't seem so dorky out in the hall.
是六张去看 “猫头鹰和河豚鱼”的票
Why,it's six tickets to Hootie and the Blowfish!
是“河豚鱼”呀
The Blowfish!
是我们付钱的，所以别担心 我们…
It's on us. So don't worry. This is...
…请客
...our treat.
谢了
Thank you.
你们为何不高兴啊
Could you be less enthused?
各位，你们一番好意
Look,it's a nice gesture. It is.
可是我们觉得这像…
But it just feels like....
像…
Like?
施舍
Charity.
施舍？
Charity?
我们只是想让大家高兴
We're just trying to do a nice thing here.
对，罗斯但是你这么做 让我们觉得我们很渺小
But you have to understand,your "nice thing" makes us feel about this big.
事实上，我们是这么小
Actually,it makes us feel that big.
我不懂 我是说，我们怎样做都不对
I don't understand. We can't win with you guys.
若你们觉得那么渺小的话 那或许不是我们的错
If you guys feel this big,maybe that's not our fault.
或许…那只是你们的感觉
Maybe that's just how you feel.
你要告诉我们有什么感受
Now you're telling us how we feel.
你看嘛，我们根本就不该提的
We never should have talked about this.
我想我不去演唱会了
I'm gonna pass on the concert.
因为我现在 不太有心情去“猫头鹰”的地方
I'm just not in a very "Hootie" place right now.
我也是 我也是
-Me neither. -Me too.
各位，我们票都已经买好了
Guys,we bought the tickets.
那你们就有多余的座位可以放你们的皇冠啊什么的
Then you'll have extra seats for all your tiaras and stuff.
你说的时候干嘛瞪着我看？
Why did you look at me when you said that?
这下子我们都不能去了
So I guess now we can't go.
你们去做你们要做的事啊 我们非得集体行动不可吗？
Do what you want. Do we always have to do everything together?
知道吗？你说得对耶
You know what? You're right.
很好
Fine.
好吧
All right.
我们就去
We're gonna go.
不过还有六个小时 我们到时候再去
It's not for another six hours. We're gonna go then.
天啊，你准备好了吗？
Are you ready?
好了，等我先拿个外套 还有我今天上床了
Just let me grab my jacket and tell you I had sex today.
什么？你今天上床了？
What? You had sex today?
从别人嘴里说出来更酷耶
It sounds even cooler when somebody else says it!
我棒透了，我害得她必须要 咬住嘴唇忍住尖叫
I was awesome. She was biting her lip to stop from screaming.
我知道我很久没有这样了 但我认为那是个好现象
I know it's been a while,but I took that as a good sign.
你还在过滤电话吗？
Still doing the screening?
我今天上床了
I had sex today.
我再也不用去接那个电话
I never have to answer that phone again.
哔一声过后，你知道怎么做
At the sound of the beep,you know what to do.
鲍勃，我是珍德，听着
Hey,Bob. It's Jade.
你那天放我鸽子 我心里难过极了
I wanted to tell you I was really hurt when you didn 't show up yesterday.
结果你知道吗？ 我认识了另一个人
And just so you know,I ended up meeting a guy.
我是鲍勃
Bob here.
你认识了别人？
So you met someone,huh?
没错
Yes,I did.
事实上 我两小时前跟他上床了
In fact,I had sex with him two hours ago.
他怎么样呢？
So how was he?
鲍勃，跟你比他算什么
Oh,Bob,he was nothing compared to you.
我得咬住嘴唇 才能不叫出你的名字
I bit my lip to keep from screaming your name.
很高兴听你这么讲
Well,that makes me feel so good.
我是觉得他好没技巧
It was just so awkward and bumpy.
或许是因为他采取了一些 你不熟悉的新的酷姿势
Maybe he had some kind of new style that you're not familiar with.
你应该要习惯他的做法呀
You have to get used to it.
根本没多少时间可以让我习惯…
There wasn 't much time to get used to it...
…懂我的意思吗？
...if you know what I mean.
知道吗？ 我想我根本没有心情听这个
You know what? I'm not gonna be able to enjoy this.
我知道，这是我的生日 我们应该全部在一起的
I know. It's my birthday. We all should be here.
那么走吧
So let's go.
或许我们应该听一首再走
Well,maybe we should stay for one song.
对呀，反正现在离开有点不敬
It would be rude to them for us to leave now.
说不定 他们现在正玩得很开心呢
The guys are probably having a great time.
来吧，再来一次嘛
Come on,you guys. One more time.
―
One.
不可思议 棒透了
-Amazing! -Excellent!
真不能相信他们错过这个
I can't believe the guys missed it!
你说谁？对了
What guys? Oh,yeah.
请问，你是莫妮卡盖勒，对吧？
Excuse me. Aren't you Monica Geller?
我认识你吗？ 你以前当过我的褓姆呀
-Do I know you? -You were my baby-sitter!
天啊，我的小史提维・费舍
Oh,my God! Little Stevie Fisher?
近来好不好啊？
How have you been?
很好，我现在是律师了
Good. I'm a lawyer now.
你不可能是律师，你才八岁
You can't be a lawyer. You're 8.
听着，很高兴见到你 我要去后台了
It was nice to see you. I gotta run backstage.
等等，后台？
Wait,backstage?
他们是我公司代理的。-我是罗斯。-钱德
My firm represents the band.-Ross.-Chandler.
你们想认识他们吗？
You guys wanna meet the group?
那走吧
Come on.
对了 你以前是跟我爸乱搞的其中之一吗？
Are you one of the ones that fooled around with my Dad?
各位
Hey,you guys!
生日快乐
Happy birthday!
谢谢
Oh,thank you.
你们昨天晚上过得怎么样？
How was your night last night?
昨晚真是烂得可以了 你们呢？
Oh,well,it pretty much sucked. How was yours?
我们也是烂得可以啊
Ours pretty much sucked too.
但是我碰到了史提维・费舍 你记得吗？
But I ran into Stevie Fisher. Remember him?
记得，我以前当过他的褓姆
Oh,yeah! I used to baby-sit him.
他爸好吗？
Hey,how's his dad?
很好
Good.
除此之外 我们昨天整个晚上都满凄惨的
Aside from that,the evening was pretty much a bust.
对，我们很想念你们
Yeah,we really missed you guys.
对呀，我们刚才还说 这件事太愚蠢了
Yeah,we were just saying,this whole thing is so stupid.
我们必须真的真的 不让钱这种事情介入…
We just have to really,really not let stuff like money,get like
那是个吻痕吗？
Is that a hickey?
不，我只是…
Oh,no,I just....
我跌倒了
I fell down.
跌在别人嘴上？
On someone's lips?
你那吻痕哪儿来的？
Where'd you get the hickey?
你知道，派对啊…
You know,a party or
什么派对？
What party?
那不算是派对…
It wasn't a party so much as a...
…只能说是一群人聚在一起
...a gathering of people.
有吃的，有音乐，还有…
With food and music and...
…乐团
...and the band.
你们跟“猫头鹰和河豚鱼”开派对？
You partied with Hootie and the Blowfish?
对，很显然史提维跟猫头鹰很熟
Yes. Apparently,Stevie and Hootie are like this.
那吻痕是谁给的？
Who gave you that hickey?
是其中一个河豚鱼弄的
That would be the work of a Blowfish.
我真不敢相信
I can't believe it! I can't believe this!
我们只是坐在家里头 猜乔伊的手指头…
We're just sitting at home,trying to guess Joey's fingers...
而你们却跑出去疯狂作乐说：
...and you're partying and having fun and all:
“嘿，河豚鱼，来吸我脖子”
"Hey,Blowfish,suck on my neck!"
不要怪我们 本来你们也可以去的
Don't blame us. You could've been there.
什么？当被你们施舍的穷朋友，是不是？
What? As part of your "poor friends outreach program"?
噢，是公司
Oh,great. It's work.
我不晓得该说什么 很抱歉我们赚的钱比你们多
I don't know what to say. I'm sorry we make more than you.
可是我们不想因此有罪恶感 我们很努力的赚钱啊
But we're not gonna feel guilty. We work really hard.
我们就不努力？
And we don't work hard?
我是莫妮卡 刚刚有人传呼我
It's Monica. I got a page.
有时候我们会想做花钱多的事情嘛
It's just that sometimes we like to do stuff that costs a little more.
是我们拖住你了。-是的，不
And you feel like we hold you back.-Yes.No
等等
Leon,wait.
各位！
Guys!
我不明白
I don't understand.
那些牛排只是肉商送来的礼物
The steaks were a gift from the meat vendor.
可不是回扣啊
That was not a kickback.
那我还他们 我们把这件事忘掉好了
I'll just replace them,and we can forget the whole thing.
什么公司政策啊？
What corporate policy?
我被开除了
I just got fired.
你们的帐单，一共四块一毛二
Here's your check. That'll be $4. 1 2.
我来付
Let me get that.
你有没有五块啊？
You got 5 bucks?
哔一声过后，你知道怎么做
Here comes the beep. You know what to do.
是我
Hi,it's me.
鲍勃 也许我不该做这样的要求
Listen,Bob. I'm probably way out of line here.
我是说都过三年了 说不定你另外有女朋友了…
It's been three years,and you 're probably seeing someone else now...
…我们如果能在一起一个晚上 看在往日的份上…
...but if we could have one night together,for old time 's sake....
干柴烈火的一晚…
One hot,steamy,wild night....